A Guide to the Graham T. T. Molitor Papers FA074
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Foreign Policy - Laos (Box 6, Folder 219)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Foreign Policy - Latin America (Box 6, Folder 220)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Foreign Policy - Southeast Asia (Box 6, Folder 221)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Foreign Policy - South Vietnam (Box 6, Folder 222)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Foreign Policy - Soviet Union (Box 6, Folder 223)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Papers - Foreign Trade (Box 6, Folder 224)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Paper - Pacifists (Box 6, Folder 225)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Paper - Peace Corps (Box 6, Folder 226)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Paper - Science and Government (Box 6, Folder 227)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Paper - Space Program (Box 6, Folder 228)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Paper - United Nations (Box 6, Folder 229)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Paper - Veterans (Box 6, Folder 230)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Paper - World Court (Box 6, Folder 231)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Campaign-Related Material - Position Paper - General (Box 6, Folder 232)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - News Clippings, May 1964 (Box 7, Folder 233)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - News Clippings, June 1964; Folder 1 of 3 (Box 7, Folder 234)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - News Clippings, June 1964; Folder 2 of 3 (Box 7, Folder 235)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - News Clippings, June 1964; Folder 3 of 3 (Box 7, Folder 236)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - News Clippings, July 1964 (Box 7, Folder 237)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - News Clippings, August 1964 (Box 7, Folder 238)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - News Clippings - Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 239)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - Column Clippings (Los Angeles Times), 1960; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 240)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - Column Clippings (Los Angeles Times), 1960; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 241)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - Column Clippings (Los Angeles Times), 1961; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 242)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - Column Clippings (Los Angeles Times), 1961; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 243)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - Column Clippings (Los Angeles Times), 1962; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 244)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - Column Clippings (Los Angeles Times), 1962; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 245)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - Column Clippings (Los Angeles Times), 1963; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 246)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - Column Clippings (Los Angeles Times), 1963; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 247)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - Column Clippings (Los Angeles Times) - "Where I Stand Columns" (Box 7, Folder 248)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - General - Retrieval System (Box 7, Folder 249)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - General - General Media Relations (Box 7, Folder 250)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - General - Adverse International Press (Box 7, Folder 251)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - General - Research Packet Sent to Issues and Answers (Box 7, Folder 252)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - General - Congressional Quarterly Presidential Coverage (Box 7, Folder 253)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Goldwater and the Press - General - Goldwater for President News Release (Box 7, Folder 254)
- Barry M. Goldwater - General Positions - Changes/Shifts, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 8, Folder 255)
- Barry M. Goldwater - General Positions - Changes/Shifts, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 8, Folder 256)
- Barry M. Goldwater - General Positions - Extreme Positions - One Sentence Type (Box 8, Folder 257)
- Barry M. Goldwater - General Positions - Extreme Positions - Rebuttal (Box 8, Folder 258)
- Barry M. Goldwater - General Positions - Extreme Positions - Extremism Plans (Box 8, Folder 259)
- Barry M. Goldwater - General Positions - Extreme Positions - General (Box 8, Folder 260)
- Barry M. Goldwater - General Positions - Extreme Positions - GOOFS (Box 8, Folder 261)
- Barry M. Goldwater - General Positions - Flip Flops - "Misrepresentation of Positions" (Box 8, Folder 262)
- Barry M. Goldwater - General Positions - Flip Flops - St. Louis Globe - Democrat (Box 8, Folder 263)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Reports - Donna Mitchell Reports, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 264)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Reports - Donna Mitchell Reports, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 265)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Reports - Donna Mitchell Reports, January 9, 1963 - August 30, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 266)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Reports - Donna Mitchell Reports, September 3, 1963 - December 6, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 267)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Reports - Donna Mitchell Reports, December 7, 1963 - August 1964 (Box 8, Folder 268)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Reports - Evans-Novak Political Report (Box 8, Folder 268A)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Personal Papers - Anti-Goldwater (Box 8, Folder 269)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Personal Papers - BMG Bibliography (Box 8, Folder 270)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Personal Papers - Candidacy (Box 8, Folder 271)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Personal Papers - BMG Criticisms: Public Figures (Box 8, Folder 272)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Personal Papers - Goldwater Family Problems (Box 8, Folder 273)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Personal Papers - GTTM Memos (Box 8, Folder 274)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Personal Papers - Hate Literature (Box 8, Folder 275)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Personal Papers - Hate Theme (Box 8, Folder 276)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Personal Papers - Job Conflict (Box 8, Folder 277)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Personal Papers - Nervous Breakdowns (Box 8, Folder 278)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Personal Papers - Underworld Association (Box 8, Folder 279)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Personal Papers - Vice President (Box 8, Folder 280)
- Barry M. Goldwater - General Files - Goldwater - General (Box 8, Folder 281)
- Barry M. Goldwater - General Files - "To Be Xeroxed" File (Box 8, Folder 282)
- Barry M. Goldwater - General Files - Miscellaneous Files (Volume I) (Box 8, Folder 283)
- Barry M. Goldwater - General Files - Barry Goldwater Misc., 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 284)
- Barry M. Goldwater - General Files - Eastern Sea Board (Box 8, Folder 285)
- Barry M. Goldwater - General Files - Miscellaneous Files (Volume II) (Box 9, Folder 286)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Bill File - Bill Recap, Folder 1 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 287)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Bill File - Bill Recap, Folder 2 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 288)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Bill File - Bill Recap, Folder 3 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 289)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Bill File - Bill Recap, Folder 4 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 290)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Bill File - Bill Digest Summary, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 9, Folder 291)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Bill File - Bill Digest Summary, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 9, Folder 292)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Bill File - Study of Number Passed (Box 9, Folder 293)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Bill File - General (Box 9, Folder 294)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Biographical Information (Box 9, Folder 295)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Book Indices (Box 9, Folder 296)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Congressional File - Congressional Record Comments (Box 9, Folder 297)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Congressional File - Congressional Record Index (Box 9, Folder 298)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Congressional File - Congressional Quarterly Report, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 9, Folder 299)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Congressional File - Congressional Quarterly Report, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 9, Folder 300)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Congressional File - Senate Roll Call - Goldwater Vote (Box 9, Folder 301)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speech-Related Material - Goldwater Questions (Box 9, Folder 302)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speech-Related Material - Questions and Answers (Box 9, Folder 303)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speech-Related Material - New Hampshire Quotes (Box 9, Folder 304)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speech-Related Material - Miscellaneous Quotes (Box 9, Folder 305)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speech-Related Material - 1 Minute Spots (Box 9, Folder 306)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speech-Related Material - Miscellaneous Interviews, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 9, Folder 307)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speech-Related Material - Miscellaneous Interviews, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 9, Folder 308)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches, Pre 1963 (Box 10, Folder 309)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches, January 17, 1963 - November 13, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 310)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches, November 16, 1963 - December 26, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 311)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches, January 1964 (Box 10, Folder 312)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches, February 1, 1964 - February 14, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 313)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches, February 20, 1964 - March 16, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 314)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches, March 17, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 315)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches, March 1964 (Box 10, Folder 316)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches, April 4, 1964 - April 20, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 317)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches, April 22, 1964 - May 15, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 318)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches, April 1964 (Box 11, Folder 319)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches, May 15, 1964 - May 27, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 320)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches, May 28, 1964 - July 10, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 321)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches, August-November, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 322)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 323)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches - Keene Speech (Box 11, Folder 324)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches - Michigan Speech (Box 11, Folder 325)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches - Speeches and Press Releases on the Senate (Box 11, Folder 326)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches - Miscellaneous Speeches, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 327)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches - Miscellaneous Speeches, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 328)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches - General - Speech Recaps, February 11, 1964 - June 4, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 329)
- Barry M. Goldwater - Speeches - General - Miscellaneous Speech Recaps (Box 11, Folder 330)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Aerospace (Box 12, Folder 331)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - The Aged, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 332)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - The Aged, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 333)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Agriculture (Box 12, Folder 334)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Arms Control and Disarmament (Box 12, Folder 335)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Arts (Box 12, Folder 336)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Balance of Payments (Box 12, Folder 337)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Civil Defense (Box 12, Folder 338)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Civil Rights (Box 12, Folder 339)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Conservation (Recreation) (Box 12, Folder 340)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Consumer Protection (Box 12, Folder 341)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Crime (Box 12, Folder 342)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Defense (Box 12, Folder 343)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Draft (Box 12, Folder 344)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Economic Policy (Box 12, Folder 345)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Education (Box 12, Folder 346)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Aid (Box 12, Folder 347)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Economic Policy (Box 12, Folder 348)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Africa (Box 12, Folder 349)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Berlin (Box 12, Folder 350)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Communism (Box 12, Folder 351)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Communist China (Box 12, Folder 352)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Eastern Europe (Box 12, Folder 353)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - East-West Trade (Box 12, Folder 354)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - England (Box 12, Folder 355)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - European Economic Community (Box 12, Folder 356)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - France (Box 12, Folder 357)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Germany (Box 12, Folder 358)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - India (Box 12, Folder 359)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Japan (Box 12, Folder 360)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Latin America (Box 12, Folder 361)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - The Middle East (Box 12, Folder 362)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - North Atlantic Treaty Organization (Box 12, Folder 363)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Southeast Asia (Box 13, Folder 364)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Soviet Union (Box 13, Folder 365)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Vietnam (Box 13, Folder 366)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Western Europe (Box 13, Folder 367)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - General (Box 13, Folder 368)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Relations (Box 13, Folder 369)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Foreign Trade (Box 13, Folder 370)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Guaranteed Annual Wage (Box 13, Folder 371)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Health (Box 13, Folder 372)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Intergovernmental Relations (Box 13, Folder 373)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - International Organizations (Box 13, Folder 374)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Labor-Management Relations (Box 13, Folder 375)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Liberal-Conservative File (Box 13, Folder 376)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Manpower (Box 13, Folder 377)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Population and Food Supply (Box 13, Folder 378)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Supreme Court (Box 13, Folder 379)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Third Party (Box 13, Folder 380)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Transportation (Box 13, Folder 381)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - The United Nations (Box 13, Folder 382)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Urban Problems (Box 13, Folder 383)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - Youth (Box 13, Folder 384)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Positions on Issues - General - Issue/Position Summaries (Box 13, Folder 385)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Campaign-Related Material (Box 14, Folder 386)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - HHH's Advanceman's Handbook (Box 14, Folder 387)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Bill File (Box 14, Folder 388)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Biographical File (Box 14, Folder 389)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - C.B. File (Box 14, Folder 390)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Credibility Gap (Box 14, Folder 391)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - New York Times News Clippings (Box 14, Folder 392)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Hatchet File (Box 14, Folder 393)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Proposed Points of Attack (Box 14, Folder 394)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Voting Record (Box 14, Folder 395)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - HHH's Weak Points (Box 14, Folder 396)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Speeches, Pre-1966 (Box 14, Folder 397)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Speeches, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 398)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Speeches - General (Box 14, Folder 399)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Speeches, January-March 1968 (Box 14, Folder 400)
- Hubert H. Humphrey - Speeches, April-July 1968 (Box 14, Folder 401)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Aerospace (Box 15, Folder 402)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - The Aged (Box 15, Folder 403)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Agriculture (Box 15, Folder 404)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Arms Control and Disarmament, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 405)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Arts (Box 15, Folder 406)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Civil Rights, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 407)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Civil Rights, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 408)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Conservation (Recreation) (Box 15, Folder 409)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Consumer Protection (Box 15, Folder 410)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Crime, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 411)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Crime, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 412)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Defense and Civil Defense, 1962-1968 (Box 15, Folder 413)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Draft (Box 15, Folder 414)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Education (Box 15, Folder 415)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Economic Policy, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 416)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Economic Policy, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 417)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Aid, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 418)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 419)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Africa, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 420)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Berlin, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 421)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Communism, 1964-1968 (Box 16, Folder 422)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Communist China, 1964-1968 (Box 16, Folder 423)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Eastern Europe, 1964-1968 (Box 16, Folder 424)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Germany, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 425)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - India, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 426)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Japan, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 427)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Latin America, 1964-1968 (Box 16, Folder 428)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - The Middle East, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 429)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 430)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Southeast Asia (Other than Vietnam), 1962-1968 (Box 16, Folder 431)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - The United Nations, 1965-1968 (Box 16, Folder 432)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - United States Relations with the U.S.S.R., 1962-1968 (Box 16, Folder 433)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Urban Problems (Box 16, Folder 434)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Vietnam Newspaper Clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 435)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Vietnam Speeches, 1962-1968 (Box 16, Folder 436)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Policy - Western Europe, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 437)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Economic Policy, 1964-1968 (Box 16, Folder 438)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Economic Policy - Balance of Payments, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 439)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Relations, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 440)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Trade, 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 441)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Foreign Trade - East-West Trade (Box 16, Folder 442)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Guaranteed Annual Wage (Box 16, Folder 443)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Health, 1968; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 444)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Health, 1968; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 445)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Intergovernmental Relations, 1962-1968 (Box 16, Folder 446)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - International Organizations, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 447)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Labor Management, 1965-1968 (Box 16, Folder 448)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Liberal-Conservative File, 1964-1968 (Box 16, Folder 449)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Manpower, 1964-1968 (Box 16, Folder 450)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Population and Food Supply, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 451)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Steel Controversy, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 452)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Supreme Court, 1961-1967 (Box 16, Folder 453)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Third Party, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 454)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Transportation, 1965-1968 (Box 16, Folder 455)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Welfare, 1964-1968 (Box 17, Folder 456)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Wiretapping, 1962-1968 (Box 17, Folder 457)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - Youth, 1964-1968 (Box 17, Folder 458)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - General - Issue/Position Summaries, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 459)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Positions on Issues - General - Kennedy/Nixon Debates, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 460)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Clippings, 1963-1968; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 461)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Clippings, 1963-1968; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 462)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Congressional File, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 463)
- Robert F. Kennedy - White House Releases, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 464)
- Robert F. Kennedy - State of the Union Address, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 465)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Campaign, 1964-1968 (Box 17, Folder 466)
- Robert F. Kennedy - C.B., 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 467)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Untitled (Box 17, Folder 468)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Biography, 1964-1968 (Box 17, Folder 469)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Committee Reports, 1965-1968 (Box 18, Folder 471)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Public Works Committee Reports, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 472)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Credibility Gap, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 473)
- Robert F. Kennedy - General, 1965-1968 (Box 18, Folder 474)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Temporary Special Hatchet, 1962-1968 (Box 18, Folder 475)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Hatchet, 1953-1968 (Box 18, Folder 476)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Hatchet, 1964-1968 (Box 18, Folder 477)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Indiana, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 478)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Newspaper Clippings, 1966-1968 (Box 18, Folder 479)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Speeches, 1962-1966 (Box 19, Folder 480)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Speeches, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 481)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Speeches, May 1968 (Box 19, Folder 482)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Speeches, April 1968 (Box 19, Folder 483)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Speeches, January-March, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 484)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Quotes from Books, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 485)
- Robert F. Kennedy - Voting Records, 1965-1967 (Box 19, Folder 486)